{
   "games":[
      {
         "id":1,
         "name":"Animals Trivia",
         "level":1,
         "description":"Do you know about animals? Prove it",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"Which one is the fastest animal on earth?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Cheetah",
                  "Elephant",
                  "Turtle",
                  "Cat"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":1
            },
            {
               "question":"How much does an elephat weigh?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "2000 kg",
                  "4000 kg",
                  "5500 kg",
                  "10000 kg"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":2
            },
            {
               "question":"Are bats mammals?",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"yes"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":2,
         "name":"Geography Trivia",
         "level":1,
         "description":"Demonstrate how much you know about Geography",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"What is Australia capital city?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Sydney",
                  "Melbourne",
                  "Perth",
                  "Canberra"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":3
            },
            {
               "question":"Which colors is Sweden flag?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Blue and yellow",
                  "Red and white",
                  "Blue and red",
                  "Green and orange"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":0
            },
            {
               "question":"South Africa shares borders with Angola",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"no"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":3,
         "name":"Music Trivia",
         "level":1,
         "description":"Put your music knowledge to the test",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"What is The Beatles first single?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Let it be",
                  "Blackbird",
                  "Love me do",
                  "Yesterday"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":2
            },
            {
               "question":"How many studio albums do Rolling Stones have?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "20",
                  "30",
                  "40",
                  "50"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":1
            },
            {
               "question":"Stairway to Heaven was written only by Jimmy Page",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"no"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":4,
         "name":"Movie Trivia",
         "level":2,
         "description":"Put your movie knowledge to the test",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"Who was the director of Kill Bill?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Martin Scorsese",
                  "David Lynch",
                  "Quentin Tarantino",
                  "Alfonso Cuaron"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":2
            },
            {
               "question":"Which actor didnt star in The Departed",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Mark Wahlberg",
                  "Brad Pitt",
                  "Matt Damon",
                  "Leonardo Di Caprio"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":1
            },
            {
               "question":"Stephen Spielberg directed Jurassic Park",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"yes"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":5,
         "name":"Sports Trivia",
         "level":2,
         "description":"If you love sports, this game is for you",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"Which olympic medallist is called The Baltimore Bullet",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Usain Bolt",
                  "Simone Biles",
                  "Quentin Tarantino",
                  "Michael Phelps"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":2
            },
            {
               "question":"Which club won the Champions League in 2021",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Chelsea F.C.",
                  "Juventus",
                  "Real Madrid",
                  "PSG"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":0
            },
            {
               "question":"Serena Williams has won more grand slams than Venus",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"yes"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":6,
         "name":"Food Trivia",
         "level":2,
         "description":"Do you think you know about food? Lets find out",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"How much caffeine needs to be taken out of coffee for it to be described as decaffeinated??",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "At least 50%",
                  "At least 75%",
                  "At least 97%",
                  "At least 99%"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":2
            },
            {
               "question":"What was the first food eaten in space?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Hot dog",
                  "Scrumbled eggs",
                  "Crackers",
                  "Apple sauce"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":3
            },
            {
               "question":"Honey cant go bad",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"yes"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":7,
         "name":"Art Trivia",
         "level":3,
         "description":"A game for art lovers",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"Who painted Woman with a Parasol?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Monet",
                  "Rembrandt",
                  "Manet",
                  "Van Gogh"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":0
            },
            {
               "question":"Who composed La Traviata",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Bellini",
                  "Verdi",
                  "Mozart",
                  "Wagner"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":1
            },
            {
               "question":"Michelangelos La Pieta can be visited at the Uffizi Gallery in Florence",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"no"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":8,
         "name":"History Trivia",
         "level":3,
         "description":"Do you think you know about history?",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"What is the earliest surviving system of laws?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Hebrew Torah",
                  "Code of Hammurabi",
                  "Shabaka Stone",
                  "Rosetta Stone"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":1
            },
            {
               "question":" What was the last battle of the Napoleonic Wars?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "Battle of Waterloo",
                  "Battle of Trafalgar",
                  "Battle of Wavre",
                  "Battle of the Nile"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":1
            },
            {
               "question":"Rome was the first city to reach a population of one million",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"yes"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id":9,
         "name":"Human Body Trivia",
         "level":3,
         "description":"Demonstrate how much you know about the human body",
         "questions":[
            {
               "question":"How many joints are in the body?",
               "type":"multiple",
               "choices":[
                  "150",
                  "177",
                  "201",
                  "230"
               ],
               "correctAnswer":3
            },
            {
               "question":"An eyelash lives about 150 days before it falls out.",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"yes"
            },
            {
               "question":"You use 43 muscles to smile and 14 to frown.",
               "type":"yesno",
               "correctAnswer":"no"
            }
         ]
      }
   ],
   "levels":[
      {
         "id":1,
         "name":"Animals Trivia",
         "level":"Beginner",
         "description":"Do you know about animals? Prove it"
      },
      {
         "id":2,
         "name":"Geography Trivia",
         "level":"Medium",
         "description":"Demonstrate how much you know about Geography"
      },
      {
         "id":3,
         "name":"Human Body Trivia",
         "level":"Expert",
         "description":"Demonstrate how much you know about the human body"
      }
   ]
}
